Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Gorgeous Dream= (Adapted from the novel "The Charming Evil Consort.")
=حلم رائع= (مقتبس من رواية "الزوجة الشريرة الساحرة").
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
(The women of the Liu clan) (Because the Liu clan head, Liu Qinghe embezzled tax silver.)
(نساء عشيرة ليو) (لأن رئيس عشيرة ليو، ليو تشينغهي، اختلس أموال الضرائب الفضية.)
(The men were exiled to the Northern Frontier.)
(تم نفي الرجال إلى الحدود الشمالية.)
(The women)
(النساء)
(were all sent into the prisonlike Jade Spy Bureau.)
(تم إرسالهم جميعًا إلى مكتب Jade Spy الذي يشبه السجن.)
(They endured hardship for four years.)
(لقد تحملوا المشقة لمدة أربع سنوات.)
(Now their suffering has finally ended.)
(لقد انتهت معاناتهم الآن أخيراً.)
(The new Emperor has granted a general pardon.)
(لقد منح الإمبراطور الجديد عفواً عاماً.)
(Liu clan, we have returned.)
(عشيرة ليو، لقد عدنا.)
We are finally home.
لقد وصلنا أخيرا إلى المنزل.
We have finally returned.
لقد عدنا أخيرا.
This is wonderful.
هذا رائع.
Yes.
نعم.
Sprinkle water to sweep away misfortune.
رش الماء ليبعد سوء الحظ.
Step over fire to welcome good fortune.
تخطي فوق النار للترحيب بالحظ السعيد.
(Prefectural Judge of Ning City, Liu Qinghe)
(قاضي مقاطعة مدينة نينغ، ليو تشينغهي)
Father.
أب.
(The Dowager of the Liu Clan) The children are here.
(أرملة عشيرة ليو) الأطفال هنا.
(Ancestral Matriarch) They have all arrived.
(الأسلاف الأم) لقد وصلوا جميعا.
Mother.
الأم.
Welcome home, everyone.
مرحباً بكم في منزلكم جميعاً.
The battle dance strengthens the spirit.
رقصة المعركة تقوي الروح.
Good fortune will never leave us.
الحظ السعيد لن يتركنا أبدًا.
Good.
جيد.
(The adopted daughter of the Liu Residence, Shen Wanqing.)
(الابنة المتبناة لعائلة ليو، شين وان تشينغ.)
Mother.
الأم.
Who are the people inside?
من هم الأشخاص بالداخل؟
Look,
ينظر،
they dance so well.
إنهم يرقصون بشكل جيد.
Brother.
أخ.
Mother, you have finally come home.
أمي، لقد عدت أخيرا إلى المنزل.
You have lived under the Liu clan's roof for years.
لقد عشت تحت سقف عشيرة ليو لسنوات.
You have enjoyed comfort and abundance.
لقد استمتعت بالراحة والوفرة.
The Liu clan has treated you as if you were their own.
لقد عاملتك عشيرة ليو كما لو كنت أحد أفرادها.
Now it is time for you to repay the kindness that raised you.
والآن حان الوقت لرد الجميل الذي ربّاك.
So
لذا
you should set out on your final journey in peace.
ينبغي عليك أن تبدأ رحلتك الأخيرة بسلام.
This...
هذا...
Brother, what do you mean?
أخي ماذا تقصد؟
You have spent four years in prison.
لقد قضيت أربع سنوات في السجن.
You have already lost your good name.
لقد فقدت بالفعل سمعتك الطيبة.
The Liu clan
عشيرة ليو
will no longer allow you to remain.
لن يسمح لك بالبقاء بعد الآن.
Our reputation is no longer what it once was.
سمعتنا لم تعد كما كانت في السابق.
Your deaths are needed to prove our loyalty.
إن موتكم ضروري لإثبات ولائنا.
If you willingly die in the name of chastity,
إذا مت طوعا باسم العفة،
you may still win the new Emperor's favor.
لا يزال بإمكانك الفوز برضا الإمبراطور الجديد.
Such a choice
مثل هذا الاختيار
will be considered a worthy death.
سيتم اعتباره موتًا يستحق الموت.
Do it.
افعلها.
Mother, go!
أمي اذهبي!
This way!
من هنا!
Hurry!
عجل!
Husband, no!
زوجي لا!
No! Stop!
لا! توقف!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Help!
يساعد!
(The son of Liu Qinghe, Liu Wenyu) Wenyu, it's me, Xiaohua! Spare me!
(ابن ليو تشينغهي، ليو وينيو) وينيو، هذا أنا، شياوهوا! أنقذني!
Enough.
كافٍ.
(The second brother of Liu Qinghe, Liu Qingming) I am sorry.
(الأخ الثاني لليو تشينغهي، ليو تشينغمينغ) أنا آسف.
This is the rule of the Liu clan.
هذه هي قاعدة عشيرة ليو.
(The younger brother of Xie Ruilan, Xie Yaozu)
(الأخ الأصغر لشيه رويلان، شيه ياوزو)
Young master.
سيد شاب.
Do not blame me.
لا تلومني.
This is your fate.
هذا هو مصيرك
Let go!
اتركه!
Everyone, let go!
الجميع، دعهم يذهبوا!
All of you, let go!
جميعكم، دعوا الأمر يمر!
Release!
يطلق!
Let go!
اتركه!
Brother.
أخ.
Because you embezzled silver,
لأنك اختلست الفضة،
we took the blame for the Liu clan.
لقد تحملنا اللوم على عشيرة ليو.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why should we be the ones who must die?
لماذا يجب علينا أن نموت؟
In the Jade Spy Bureau,
في مكتب جايد للتجسس،
it was we who endured every torment.
لقد كنا نحن الذين تحملنا كل العذاب.
- Why? - Wanqing!
لماذا؟ وانكينج!
Wanqing!
أنتم من يجب أن يموتوا!
It is you!
إنه أنت!
Move!
يتحرك!
Have them open the door!
اطلب منهم أن يفتحوا الباب!
Say it!
قلها!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Mother.
الأم.
I will never allow anyone to tarnish
لن اسمح لأحد أن يشوه سمعتي أبدًا
the good name of the Liu clan.
الاسم الجيد لعشيرة ليو.
Mother.
الأم.
Why will you not listen to my son?
لماذا لا تستمع إلى ابني؟
Listen to my son!
إستمع إلى ابني!
No!
لا!
My son, Qinghe
ابني، تشينغهي
has struggled bitterly to reach this day.
لقد ناضل بشدة للوصول إلى هذا اليوم.
Your sacrifice
تضحياتك
will become the foundation of the Liu clan.
سيصبح الأساس لعشيرة ليو.
To die for the family
الموت من أجل العائلة
is the highest honor for us women.
هو أعظم شرف لنا نحن النساء.
My son is right.
ابني على حق.
From this day on,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
our names will be written separately in the family registry.
سيتم كتابة أسمائنا بشكل منفصل في سجل العائلة.
The ancestral hall will bear our names.
القاعة الأجدادية ستحمل أسماءنا.
Our fathers and brothers,
آبائنا وإخوتنا،
our husbands,
أزواجنا
our children,
اطفالنا
and our families
وعائلاتنا
will all be proud of us.
وسوف يكون الجميع فخورين بنا.
The Ancestress has acted with great righteousness.
لقد تصرفت الجدة بصلاح عظيم.
We respectfully send the Ancestress on her final journey.
نرسل بكل احترام الجدة في رحلتها الأخيرة.
My son...
ابني...
From this day forward,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
Liu clan
عشيرة ليو
will be entrusted to you.
سيتم تسليمها إليك.
We spent a great deal to bring you here.
لقد أنفقنا الكثير من المال لإحضارك إلى هنا.
You must handle everything perfectly.
يجب عليك التعامل مع كل شيء بشكل مثالي.
Sister.
أخت.
(The matriarch of the Liu clan, Xie Ruilan) No one must notice anything amiss.
(أم عشيرة ليو، شي رويلان) لا ينبغي لأحد أن يلاحظ أي شيء خاطئ.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I promise I will take care of everything flawlessly.
أعدك بأنني سأعتني بكل شيء على أكمل وجه.
Even if the authorities investigate,
حتى لو قامت السلطات بالتحقيق،
they will find nothing but a case of self-immolation.
فلن يجدوا إلا حالة من الانتحار حرقاً.
Shen Wanqing.
شين وان تشينغ.
You are no adopted daughter of the Liu Residence.
أنت لست ابنة بالتبني لعائلة ليو.
You were nothing more than
لم تكن أكثر من ذلك
an orphan we seized for ourselves.
يتيمة أخذناها لأنفسنا.
Through your deaths,
من خلال موتك،
the chastity memorial we earn
نصب العفة الذي ننال
can exempt us from three years of tax.
يمكن أن يعفينا من ثلاث سنوات من الضرائب.
It can be exchanged for ten thousand taels.
يمكن استبداله بعشرة آلاف تايل.
Do not blame me.
لا تلومني.
If you must blame someone,
إذا كان لا بد من إلقاء اللوم على شخص ما،
blame this cruel world that devours people.
اللوم على هذا العالم القاسي الذي يلتهم الناس.
Your identity as the last orphan of the Shen family
هويتك كاليتيم الأخير لعائلة شين
from this moment on
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا
will forever remain a secret.
سوف تبقى سرا إلى الأبد.
To die under the name of The Seven Martyr Heroines
الموت تحت اسم البطلات السبع الشهيدات
is the finest end you could hope for.
هي أفضل نهاية يمكنك أن تأمل فيها.
Your name will be remembered.
سيتم تذكر اسمك.
The world will speak of you.
العالم سوف يتحدث عنك .
You need not thank me.
لا داعي لأن تشكرني.
(The spirit tablets of Martyr Liu Wangshu, Martyr Li Shushen, and Martyr Liu Mingzhen)
(الألواح الروحية للشهيد ليو وانغشو، والشهيد لي شوشن، والشهيد ليو مينغ تشن)
(Just as Liu Qinghe wished.)
(كما تمنى ليو تشينغهي.)
(The spirit tablet of Martyr Shen Wanqing) (The Emperor honors the sacrifice of The Seven Martyr Heroines.)
(اللوح الروحي للشهيدة شين وان تشينغ) (الإمبراطور يكرم تضحية البطلات السبع الشهيدات.)
(A Household of Chastity) (The Liu clan is greatly rewarded.)
(بيت العفة) (تحظى عشيرة ليو بمكافأة عظيمة.)
(A gilded plaque proclaiming their purity)
(لوحة مذهبة تعلن عن نقائهم)
(is hung high.)
(معلقة عاليا.)
(And Liu Qinghe)
(وليو تشينغهي)
(is promoted to Prefectural Judge of Ning City.)
(تم ترقيته إلى منصب قاضي مقاطعة مدينة نينغ.)
(Mother.)
(الأم.)
(Wanqing.)
(وانكينج.)
(A Household of Chastity) (Your sacrifices were worth it.)
(بيت العفة) (تضحياتكم كانت تستحق ذلك.)
(You now wear a new face.)
(أنت الآن ترتدي وجهًا جديدًا.)
(From this moment on, Shen Wanqing no longer exists.)
(من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، لم يعد شين وانكينج موجودا.)
(The Liu clan's blood feud)
(الثأر الدموي لعشيرة ليو)
(do you still intend to avenge it?)
(هل لا تزال تنوي الانتقام؟)
(This new face)
(هذا الوجه الجديد)
(is gentle,)
(لطيف)
(obedient,)
(مطيع،)
(and harmless.)
(وغير ضارة.)
(It is exactly the type those bandits favor most.)
(إنه بالضبط النوع الذي يفضله هؤلاء اللصوص أكثر.)
(As long as the lie of the Liu clan's martyrdom remains unbroken,)
(ما دامت كذبة استشهاد عشيرة ليو لم تنكسر)
(those orphaned girls)
(هؤلاء الفتيات اليتيمات)
(will forever be recorded in their ledgers)
(سيتم تسجيلها إلى الأبد في دفاترهم)
(as wrongful sacrifices.)
(كتضحيات خاطئة)
(Happiness) (I will appear before each of them)
(السعادة) (سأظهر أمام كل واحد منهم)
(in the very form they adored)
(بالشكل الذي يعشقونه)
(at their funerals.)
(في جنازاتهم.)
(Three years later, Ning City)
(بعد ثلاث سنوات، مدينة نينغ)
(Happiness)
(سعادة)
(The son of Liu Qinghe, Liu Wenyu.)
(ابن ليو تشينغهي، ليو وينيو.)
The auspicious hour has arrived.
لقد حانت الساعة الميمونة.
The bride enters the residence.
العروس تدخل إلى المسكن.
(Happiness) First, sprinkle pomelo water to purify all defilement.
(السعادة) أولاً، رش ماء الجريب فروت لتطهير كل الأوساخ.
Second, step over the fire basin to welcome good fortune.
ثانياً، اقفز فوق حوض النار للترحيب بالحظ السعيد.
May the household prosper and enjoy a hundred years of peace.
نرجو أن ينعم البيت بالرخاء وأن يتمتع بمائة عام من السلام.
The bride looks unfamiliar.
العروس تبدو غير مألوفة.
She must be from another town.
لا بد أنها من مدينة أخرى.
I heard that this bride,
سمعت أن هذه العروسة،
though merely the daughter of a merchant,
على الرغم من كونها مجرد ابنة تاجر،
(Huan Xi, maid of Lan Mengyan) comes from the wealthiest family in Yang City.
(هوان شي، خادمة لان مينجيان) تأتي من أغنى عائلة في مدينة يانغ.
Look at her dowry.
أنظر إلى مهرها.
Who here could compare?
من هنا يمكن مقارنته؟
What good is being wealthy?
ما فائدة أن تكون ثريا؟
She is still a parentless orphan.
وهي لا تزال يتيمة بلا أبوين.
Once she enters the Liu Residence, her days may not be easy.
بمجرد دخولها إلى مقر إقامة ليو، قد لا تكون أيامها سهلة.
(The younger brother of Xie Ruilan, Xie Yaozu.)
(الأخ الأصغر لـ Xie Ruilan، Xie Yaozu.)
(Happiness)
(سعادة)
Qing.
تشينغ.
We are home.
نحن في المنزل.
Do not be shy.
لا تكن خجولا.
Let me introduce my family to you.
دعوني أقدم لكم عائلتي.
Mother, this is Lan Mengyan.
أمي، هذا لان مينجيان.
The dowry is complete, Sister.
المهر كامل يا أختي.
Excellent.
ممتاز.
(The Liu clan,)
(عشيرة ليو)
(I have returned.)
(لقد عدت.)